paper4pc.com 2017-02-18

# Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Policy

1\. We collect

Our servers are designed to automatically record information about your activity on our website which also includes all the information sent by your browser time to time. This information includes differnet things such as your IP address, name of type of the browser you are using and also the webpage you were visiting before you came to http://paper4pc.com. It also includes the data about your Windows and the language you are using.

2\. Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. paper4pc.com uses cookies to help paper4pc.com identify and track visitors, their usage of paper4pc.com website, and their website access preferences. Automattic visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Automattic’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Automattic’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

3\. DoubleClick Cookies

Cookies can also be used for ad serving through Google DoubleClick which stores a cookie on your PC while you are browsing a website and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (this may also include some of the Google AdSense advertisements). Interest based targeting can also be enable through cookies which shows specific ads to you according to your preferences. Ads shown to you will be based on your previous browsing history so that only relevant ads are shown to you. (For example, if you have been visiting cooking sites, you may visit a cooking website while visiting a non-relevant site such as a sports website). It is to be made sure that it does NOT track your personal information such as your name, email address, physicall address, IP address, telephone number, social security number, bank accoutn number or credit card number etc. You also have the option to opt out of this ad-serving on all the sites using the link http://www.google.com/doubleclick/ .

Here you can choose to disable or selectively turn on off your cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings. Also this is the page you should visit to set any preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  
In short, this affects how you interact with our site as well as the other sites. This may also include the inability to login to service programs, such as logging into forums and accounts. However, it is also to be remembered that deleting cookies will not allow you to permanently opt out of any advertising programs.

4\. Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, paper4pc.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in paper4pc.com’s sole discretion. paper4pc.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
